Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Political Polling Books, 1968-1994 (Box 162-193)
  - 642-017-001. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Dakota, January 13, 1988 (Box 178)
  - 642-017-001. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Dakota, January 13, 1988 (Box 178)
  - 642-017-001. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Dakota, January 13, 1988 (Box 178)
  - 642-017-001. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Dakota, January 13, 1988 (Box 179)
  - 648-020-003. Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in Washington, September 1, 1984 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-001. New Progressive Party: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 15, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-002. New Progressive Party: An IN-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, December 6, 1982 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-003. Partido Nuevo Progresivo: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan Puerto Rico - Governor, June 1, 1983 (Box 179)
  - 662-001-003. Partido Nuevo Progresivo: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan Puerto Rico - Governor, June 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-003. Partido Nuevo Progresivo: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan Puerto Rico - Governor, June 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-004. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: An In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-004. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: An In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-004. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: An In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-004. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: An In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1983 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-007. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 8, 1984 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-008. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, July 1, 1984 (Box 180)
  - 662-001-008. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, July 1, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-001-008. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, July 1, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-001-015. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico (Island Wide), September 4, 1985 (Box 181)
  - 662-001-015. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico (Island Wide), September 4, 1985 (Box 181)
  - 662-001-015. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico (Island Wide), September 4, 1985 (Box 181)
  - 662-001-011. Barcelo, Carlos Ramiro: In-home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico, August 29, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-002. Baltasar Corrada del Rio: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico - Mayor, December 16, 1983 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-002. Partido Nuevo Progresivo: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico - Governor, December 16, 1983 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-002. Baltasar Corrada del Rio: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico - Mayor, December 16, 1983 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-003. Baltasar Corrada del Rio: An In-home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, May 22, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-004. Partido Nuevo Progresivo: An In-home Survey of Voter Attitudes in San Juan, Puerto Rico, July 16, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-002-006. Baltasar Corrada del Rio: In-Home Survey of Voter Attitudes in Puerto Rico (Island Wide), October 1, 1984 (Box 181)
  - 662-003-001.: A Survey of Attitudes in Puerto Rico, October 1, 1987 (Box 181)
  - 664-001-001. PAN Party: Nuevo Leon, May 1, 1985 (Box 181)
  - 664-001-001. PAN Party: Nuevo Leon, May 1, 1985 (Box 181)
  - 665-002-001. Italian Christian Democratic Party (La Democrazia Cristiana): A Study of Registered Voters in Sicily: "Project Falcon,", May 1, 1986 (Box 182)
  - 665-002-001. Italian Christian Democratic Party (La Democrazia Cristiana): A Study of Registered Voters in Sicily: "Project Falcon,", May 1, 1986 (Box 182)
  - 669-001-013. British Conservative Party: UK Pulseline, October 9, 1990 (Box 182)
  - 669-001-015. Conservative Central Office: Analysis of Issues, Values, and Party Support, December 1, 1990 (Box 182)
  - 669-001-020. British Conservative Party: Open-Ended Analysis Hazel Grove: Constituency Survey, January 6, 1992 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up Telephone Survey of Republicans in Florida, February 19, 1987 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 182)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 698-011-001. Robert Dole for President: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 (Box 183)
  - 699-001-015. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle III, February 1, 1981 (Box 183)
  - 669-001-018. Brendan P Murphy Associates: John Major - Southport & Sue Lawley: Audience Reactions, Attitudes, and Understanding, June 1, 1991 (Box 183)
  - 669-001-018. Brendan P Murphy Associates: John Major - Southport & Sue Lawley: Audience Reactions, Attitudes, and Understanding, June 1, 1991 (Box 183)
  - 669-001-018. Brendan P Murphy Associates: Party Political Broadcasts, June 1, 1991 (Box 183)
  - 669-001-018. Brendan P Murphy Associates: Party Political Broadcasts, June 1, 1991 (Box 183)
  - 699-001-022. American Medical Political Action Committee: National Post Election Study of Voter Attitudes, November 6, 1974 (Box 183)
  - 699-006-001. Ford, Gerald: A Survey of Attitudes Toward Private Enterprise, March 13, 1975 (Box 184)
  - 699-008-004. National Rifle Association: A National Survey of the American Electorate, May 19, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-008-006. National Rifle Association: A Telephone Survey of the American Electorate, December 9, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 184)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 186)
  - 699-015-001. John Sununu for Senate: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in New Hampshire, May 16, 1980 (Box 186)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 186)
  - 699-015-001. RCCC: Post Election Study 1978, November 5, 1978 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 186)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 186)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 186)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 186)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 186)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 187)
  - 699-020-001. Institute Of Arab Studies: Natl. Tele. Survey of Attitudes Concerning the Middle East, November 6, 1982 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-002. NRSC: National Tracking of Voter Attitudes, July 1, 1984 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-005. NRSC: September Quorum, September 18, 1988 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-005. NRSC: September Quorum, September 18, 1988 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-006. NRSC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 17, 1989 (Box 187)
  - 699-024-021. NRSC: 1990 Post Election, November 8, 1990 (Box 187)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 187)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 187)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 187)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 188)
  - 699-036-001. Robert Dole for President: A National Panel Survey of Republican Attitudes, November 11, 1987 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-002. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Survey of Republican Attitudes in Iowa, November 18, 1987 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 189)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 190)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 190)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 190)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 190)
  - 699-036-003. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Follow-up National Panel Survey of Republicans, January 23, 1988 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-001. House (Neil Newhouse): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 17, 1989 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-001. House (Neil Newhouse): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 17, 1989 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-001. House (Neil Newhouse): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 17, 1989 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-001. House (Neil Newhouse): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 17, 1989 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-049. House (RBW): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 4, 1992 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-048. House (RBW): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1992 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-049. House (RBW): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 4, 1992 (Box 190)
  - 699-042-044. House (RBW): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, November 4, 1991 (Box 191)
  - 699-042-048. House (RBW): A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1992 (Box 191)
  - 699-036-002. Dole, Robert (Senator): A Survey of Republican Attitudes in Iowa, November 18, 1987 (Box 191)
  - 699-043-003. National Right to Life Committee: A National Survey of Voter Attitudes, November 8, 1990 (Box 191)
  - 699-043-006. National Right to Life Committee: February Quorum, February 3, 1992 (Box 191)
  - 699-043-011. National Right to Life Committee: 1994 Post Election National Study, November 9, 1994 (Box 191)
  - 699-043-011. National Right to Life Committee: 1994 Post Election National Study, November 9, 1994 (Box 191)
  - 699-043-011. National Right to Life Committee: 1994 Post Election National Study, November 9, 1994 (Box 191)
  - 624-024-001. National Right to Life Committee: Brushfire Survey in the Sixth Congressional District of Minnesota, August 2-3, 1994 (Box 192)
  - 630-004-001. John Sununu for Senate: Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in New Hampshire, May 1, 1980 (Box 192)
  - 644-023-004.: Rhode Island Survey, May 1, 1984 (Box 192)
  - Scranton for Governor Committee: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, Feb 28-Mar 2, 1986 (Box 192)
  - Scranton for Governor Committee: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, Jun 15-17, 1986 (Box 192)
  - Scranton for Governor Committee: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, Sep 2-4, 1986 (Box 192)
  - Barry Goldwater: Survey of Arizona Voters (2 volumes), Feb 15-27, 1968 (Box 192)
  - Senator Pete Domenici: A Summary of Voter Attitudes in the State of New Mexico, Sept 1977-March 1982 (Box 193)
  - RNC: A New York Statewide Survey for the NY Republican Party, Sep 27-Oct 2, 1989 (Box 193)
  - Personal and Public Perspectives on the Reagan Presidency, March 28, 1991 (Box 193)
  - Post-Election National, November 9, 1994 (Box 193)
  - International Paper Company: Executive Summary, July 16, 1987 (Box 193)
  - Senator Robert Dole: A Follow Up Telephone Survey of Republican Attitudes in the State of New Hampshire, February 1988 (Box 193)
  - Senator Robert Dole: Survey of Republican Attitudes in the State of Iowa, December 4, 1987 (Box 193)
  - Partido Nuevo Progresista: An Analysis of Political Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 1980 (Box 193)
  - Partido Nuevo Progresista: An Analysis of Political Attitudes in Puerto Rico, May 1980 (Box 193)
  - Time of Vote and Anderson Vote, August 28, 1984 (Box 193)
  - Senator Paul Laxalt: Executive Interviews, August 14, 1985 (Box 193)
  - Senator Paul Laxalt: A Survey of Adult Americans, June 16-18, 1987 (Box 193)
  - The Arthur S. DeMoss Foundation: Impact of the Advertising Campaign, "Life, What a Beautiful Choice" on American Attitudes Towards Abortion, November 1993 (Box 193)
- Incremental Reagan Books, 1968-1988 (Box 194-204)
  Arranged by client or title, then by date. Please note that the box numbers are not in order for this group of books.
  - Campaign Action Plan: Baby Boomers, May 1, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Hispanics Constituency, July 20, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Senior Constituency, July 20, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Farm Belt Constituency, 20 July 1984 (Box 200)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Jewish Constituency, August 17, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Base Republican Constituency, August 27, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Catholics, July 1984 (Box 199)
  - Campaign Action Plan: Women's Constituency, July 1984 (Box 199)
  - CBS News/New York Times: Post Election National Survey, 1980 (Box 203)
  - Citizens for Reagan: A Survey of Republican Voters in Indiana, April 1976 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for Reagan: National Aggregates, December 1975 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for Reagan: National Panel Survey of the American Electorate: Special Report on Ballots, December 1975 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for Reagan: Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 1975 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for Reagan: A Survey of Republicans in North Carolina, February 1976 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for Reagan: National Survey of the American Electorate, June 1976 (Box 196)
  - Citizens for Reagan: National Survey of the American Electorate, September 1975 (Box 197)
  - Citizens for the Republic: A National Post-Election Survey of the 1976 Presieential Election, December 1976 (Box 196)
  - Citizens for the Republic: National Post-Election Survey of the 1976 Presidential Election, December 1976 (Box 198)
  - Gov Reagan: California Statewide, December 3-6, 1968 (Box 196)
  - Gov Reagan: Various Polls, undated (Box 195)
  - Indiana Republican State Committee: Indiana Statewide Tracking Survey, October 17, 1980 (Box 200)
  - Memorandum to Richard Wirthlin: President Reagan's Speech to the United Nations, November 1, 1985 (Box 197)
  - New York Times: Post Election National Survey, 1980 (Box 203)
  - Reagan: Reagan Campaign Action Plan, October 27, 1983 (Box 195)
  - Reagan -Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of New Jersey, June 16-18, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan for President Committee: Statewide Survey of Republican Primary Voters in New Hampshire, January 1980 (Box 196)
  - Reagan for President Committee: A Statewide Survey of Voters in Florida, June 1980 (Box 196)
  - Reagan for President Committee: Statewide Survey of Voters in New jersey, June 1980 (Box 196)
  - Reagan for President Committee: Louisiana Statewide Presidential Survey, September 1980 (Box 200)
  - Reagan/Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Deleware Voters, February 10-13, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan/Bush Committee: Louisiana Statewide, August 1980 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Missouri Statewide Tracking, September 26, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Missouri Statewide Tracking, October 20, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, October 22, 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Missouri Statewide Tracking, November 2, 1980 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, November 2, 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Michigan Statewide Survey, August 1980 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Ohio Statewide, August 20-28, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, August 20-28, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: New York Statewide, July 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Oregon Wave II, October 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Ohio Statewide, September 12-15, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Pennsylvania Statewide Survey, September 12-15, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Michigan Statewide Survey, September 1980 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Wisconsin Statewide Study, September 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Ohio Statewide, September 26-30, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '80: Ohio Statewide, September 26-30, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Oklahoma VOters, October 22, 1980 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Presidential Trackings, October 23, 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Presidential Trackings, October 24, 1980 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Alabama Survey Flash Results, June 14, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Farm Belt States Plan, August 27, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: New Jersey State Plan, September 3, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Percpetions in the State of Texas, October 4, 1984 (Box 204)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Arkansas, October 5, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Kentucky, October 5, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Massachusetts, October 9, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Ohio (II), October 25, 1984 (Box 202)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Rhode Island Satewide Tracking, October 30, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of New Jersey Voters, Agust 2-10, 1984 (Box 201)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Tennessee Voters, April 18-24, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Tennessee, April 18-24, 1984 (Box 199)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Illinois Voters, April 18-May 2, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Illinois Voters, April 18-May 2, 1984 (Box 200)
  - Reagan-Bush '84: Statewide Survey of Vermont Voters, April 28-March 26, 1984 (Box 204)